What do you even
have to back it up?
There were eyewitnesses.
A man fitting
Macher's description
was spotted at a sorority party
at Windsor College in 1997.
The same year
the murders took place.
It's complete speculation,
all right?
That's never been confirmed.
It has been con...
Holy shit.
Ugh, that was a long drive.
Holy fucking shit!
Can you get a photo of me?
Yeah.
All right. Cute.
I got it.
Wait, one more.
One more.
Okay, I have to pee.
Let's go inside.
The code is...
7-8-2-2.
Are you ready for...
the Macher House Experience?
Wow.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Ugh.
Incredible.
Whoa.
A real-life murder house.
It's perfect.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
I mean, it's like...
it's identical.
Oh, this is cool.
The fake blood.
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Check it out. Check it out.
Ugh, I'm gonna pee my pants.
Babe, this is
where Sidney Prescott
shot Billy Loomis in the face
right after she...
Stabbed him with
the umbrella. I know.
Where's the bathroom?
Oh, no, that's the closet
Sidney was hiding in.
Remember? Before she stabbed
him with the umbrella?
Duh.
Oh, I found it!
Oh.
So cool.
Ah.
This is so cool!
Incredible.
Amber.
And Richie. I mean...
Ooh.
Scott?
Hello?
Scott!
Dude, where'd you go?
Whoa. What's wrong?
Oh, my God!
Ghostface is in there!
What?
Someone with a ghost mask on.
What are you talking about?
There's somebody in that room
with a Ghostface mask on.
Oh...
Do not go in there.
Scott. Scott!
Ooh!
You're going to die tonight!
It's fake.
Oh, that is so cool.
It's got a motion sensor.
Look at this.
Do you like scary movies?
I mean, come on, look at that.
That's so cool.
Pretty hi-tech.
It looked so real.
That is sweet!
Wow.
It's plugged in
right here.
What?
Ah, so this is it.
This is so creepy.
The room where
Stu held that party
to lure Sidney Prescott
to her death.
You know, they say Billy
was the mastermind,
but I've always been
more of a Stu-head.
Who was your favorite?
What?
My favorite homicidal teenager?
Neither.
Are you gonna be like this
the whole time?
What do you want me to do?
Um...
Okay. Babe,
did you know that this is
where Sidney dropped a TV
on Stu's head?
Squished all the crazy
out of his brain?
Ah, but did she kill him?
You heard the podcast.
There's a lot of theories
out there that Stu survived.
No.
There was a dead body.
It was taken to the morgue
and then buried.
You can't fake that.
Let's check out the kitchen.
Ooh.
Oh, this is where Sidney
and Gale Weathers
roasted Amber Freeman
a few years ago.
Yeah, where she was torched.
I would hate to die that way.
Oh, my God.
It's fake.
Fucking hilarious.
It's happening.
Hello?
Hello, Scott. Hello, Madison.
Welcome to
the Macher House Experience.
Enjoying it so far?
It's amazing.
Mm-hmm.
Do you like scary movies?
Go, go.
Uh, yeah, my boyfriend's
a big horror fan.
What's your favorite
scary movie?
Stab One.
It's time to play a game.
Scary Movie Trivia.
Three questions.
Get one wrong, and you die.
Question one:
In the original
A Nightmare on Elm Street,
who is the first person to die?
Tina Gray.
Correct.
Question two:
In The People Under the Stairs,
what's the name of
Mommy and Daddy's daughter?
Alice.
Very good.
Let's try a hard one this time.
In Friday the 13th,
how old was Jason Voorhees
when he drowned?
Okay, well, in The Final Chapter
we found out Mrs. Voorhees
gave birth in 1946, right?
And then in the original,
the two counselors died
in the flashback in '58.
Jason drowned the summer
before that. That's '57.
So born in '46, drowned in '57.
Eleven. Jason was eleven.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Scott,
but that's incorrect.
Bullshit.
No, the math was right.
It's a trick question.
Jason never drowned.
Very impressive, Madison.
Scott's lucky he has you
to lean on.
I guess I don't get to stab
you guys after all.
You two have a chilling night.
And don't forget to give us
a five-star...
Are you miserable?
I wish I could fake it better.
Why'd you come here with me?
Well, you were pushy about it!
And I thought I could be cool,
then we got here
and it's so cheesy.
You want to go?
I don't want to be here
if you don't.
I can drive home right now.
You would drive home right now?
I would.
No, it's too late.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna try harder.
I promise.
Okay, now I have to pee.
It's the hallway on the left.
Hello?
You're going to die tonight.
Scott, why are you calling me?
It's not Scott.
Okay.
Who is it then?
The person who's gonna kill you.
The scary voice thing is
a little bit sexy,
but you could work on it.
Listen, you little bitch,
I'm gonna slice you open
and rip your guts out!
Did you just call me a bitch?
Okay, I said I would try,
but I'm done. This isn't fun.
Because the fun part
is over, Madison.
Scott?
They'd never make it in time.
Scott!
We're not finished yet.
Fuck you!
Stu...
Ow! Ow!
It's me.
What the fuck?
You hit me.
What is wrong with you?
I'm sorry. I thought it...
You said you were gonna try.
It was a bad idea.
Yeah, of course it was
a bad fucking idea!
It moved.
Yeah, it's electric.
That's what it does.
No. Like, it moved
differently.
What?
Oh!
No!
Fuck you!
No! No, no, no. No, no, no.
Jesus, you scared me.
You're gonna give me
a heart attack.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Well...
it occurred to me
that I've never snuck through
your bedroom window.
I was home, bored,
watching TV...
Mmm.
And Stab was on.
And that just got me
thinking of you.
That's horrific.
Billy snuck through
Sidney's window, so...
Mm-hmm.
I'm well aware.
You know,
if my mom catches you...
Mmm. Just a kiss.
Hey.
Hi.
Oh!
Can you knock?
I did.
Can you wait for a response?
Something wrong?
No.
No, everything's fine.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Ben, how you doing over there?
On the floor. Behind the bed.
Hello, Mrs. Evans.
How are you this evening?
Oh, well, I'm tired.
Ben, it's late.
That's why I didn't want to
disturb anyone by...
using the door.
So thoughtful.
Out.
But he's here now.
No.
That's okay. I'm going.
Good night, Tate.
I know it's late.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Evans.
That was on me.
Tatum had no idea
that I was coming over.
Okay, well,
let's not do it again.
I'm a good guy, Mrs. Evans.
Good night, Ben.
Hypocrite.
It's not like a boy's never
crawled through your window.
We've all seen the movie.
Which is why it's never
gonna happen in this house.
Why do you not like him?
I don't not like him.
I just...
I want you to be smart.
And not trust him so easily.
We're not having sex,
if that's
what you're worried about.
I mean, we want to,
but I don't think we're ready.
Well, if you're asking
the question, then, um...
you're probably not.
How did you know?
I mean,
did that really happen to you?
Like in the movie?
It's freezing in here.
How about we have
these kinds of conversations
during waking hours, okay?
No more boys in windows, please.
Night.
How ugly did it get?
I was extremely polite.
You know,
she's not the first girl
to let a boy
sneak in her window.
Yeah. She made that point.
You know, if being
an overprotective mom
is the worst thing she can
say about me...
I think I can live with that.
You think they're doing it?
Oh, God, no.
No. Not yet.
But I think we've got
about five minutes left.
How old were you
when you started?
Same age as you. Seventeen.
Oh, did I say seventeen?
I think I meant fifteen.
Did you lie to me?
Look, in my defense,
I don't remember.
Oh, you don't remember
the first time you had sex?
Oh, no, I don't remember
what I told you.
Oh, you told me seventeen.
Look, I didn't want to
come off as, you know...
Uh-huh. Keep going.
I want to see where this goes.
I just wanted you to see me
as more than a sex slave.
Oh. You have a mind, too?
You know... well, yeah.
Morning, Chief.
Hey, Woody. Look at that,
the walls are up, right?
Looks great.
Love you.
I love you, too.
We miss you guys.
Construction's coming along.
We're keeping them busy.
- Oh. Hey, Mom.
- Hi there, baby.
Hi, Daddy.
Thanks, Junie.
I'm glad you're having fun.
If you need anything, call.
Okay.
I love you. Thank you
for watching the maniacs.
We'll see you this weekend.
Bye.
She's very brave.
Yep.
What?
Where'd you find that?
Um, the attic.
I was looking through
some old clothes.
Do you not want me to wear it?
You could have asked.
Honey, maybe take it off.
What age do they get nice again?
That was on you.
You can wear the jacket.
It's okay, I'm good.
Tatum, I'm sorry.
Okay? It caught me off guard.
I hadn't seen it since college.
I thought I'd gotten rid of it.
Yeah, the mysterious
one semester at Windsor
we can't talk about.
That's not true.
Really? Since when?
Your childhood is
completely off-limits.
What are you talking about?
It's not off-limits.
It's online and in movies
and in books.
You could do a deep dive
whenever you want.
As long as
I don't ask questions.
You have rehearsal today?
Yep.
How's it going?
Horrible.
Tragic.
I get so nervous onstage,
it's painful to watch.
Oh, God! I used to
get stage fright.
I know the feeling.
You did theater?
Not since college.
Anyway, don't worry.
You're gonna do great.
I got to get to work.
Fucking motherhood.
Great talk.
Morning.
Hey, morning.
We'll have that
right out for you. Okay?
All right. Thank you.
Busy?
Little AM rush,
but not too bad.
Good.
Hey, Mrs. Evans.
Hey, Lucas.
Oh, could I get
four espresso shots, please?
Yeah. For sure.
Four?
Yeah.
Rehearsal today.
It's gonna be a long one.
What part do you play?
Oh, just a techie. Yeah.
I work the, uh...
the lighting board.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Hey, an old Dateline
was on last night
about the Ghostface Killers
in New York.
Have you, uh...
Have you seen it?
No, I haven't.
It's not as good as the
Netflix doc, but it's decent.
They did a good job
covering the aftermath.
Morning.
Hey.
Did you say anything?
Mm-mmm.
Did he ask you about Dateline?
It's fine, really.
No, it isn't.
I told you not to.
Ow!
That hurt.
Good.
I'm a crime junkie, Mom.
It's my... It's my thing.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Evans.
But I really want to
start a podcast,
and I think the New York murders
would be a primo first case.
Don't you have
rehearsal now, honey?
Right?
Yes.
So you should leave now.
Right. Yeah. Okay.
Okay. Great.
Bye.
Bye!
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
What'll you have?
Hey, wait up!
- Oh, hey.
- Hi!
You look hot.
Where'd you get the jacket?
Thanks. It's my mom's.
'90s vintage.
You should bedazzle it.
Yes.
Oh! Tonight,
my place, party.
I've been stockpiling
my mom's edibles.
And you can even
invite creepy boy.
Listen, he's not creepy.
Mmm.
He's deep.
And he has a squeezy butt.
Ew.
The true crime is cringy.
He's obsessed with my mom.
Is your mom gonna let you out
of your cage tonight?
I... I don't know.
Honestly,
she's been on overdrive
with the mama trauma.
Well, if anyone has a right
to be insane, it is your mom.
Very true. I've seen
all the Stab movies.
Personally, I don't know how
she's not in a psych ward.
Oh.
- Look who it is.
- Hey!
Top of the morning!
Hey, Tay.
Hey, babe.
Hiya.
You all need a lift?
You guys, come on!
Yes!
We don't have to walk anymore.
Let's go!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Buckle up.
Buckle up. Buckle up!
Karl!
Thank you.
I am so sorry about Lucas.
No.
It's just you're like
a celebrity to him.
You feel like
you guys are close, right?
Yeah. I mean, I suppose
we've had to be
since it's just the two of us.
Do you ever talk to him about
your life before you had him?
No.
No?
No, no. I mean,
there's not much I can say
about his abusive asshole father
and how badly our marriage
fucked me up.
Why? What's going on?
Oh, I don't know. Uh...
Tatum and I are having
a bit of a rough patch.
She's at that age where she
wants to know about my past.
And as you know, my past
is full of dead people.
Not exactly something
I want to share with her.
So I get quiet,
and then she gets loud,
and around and around we go.
Listen. She's your daughter,
and it's natural
she should want to know you.
You know, I just...
I want my kids to be able
to be who they are
without living in fear.
I want them to feel safe
and protected.
But it's not a safe world, Sid.
And if we protect
our children too much,
they'll never learn
how to protect themselves.
Oh, fuck!
Watch out!
Sorry.
Fuck me.
I'm stuck!
No.
No. Uh, houselights, please.
Where's Aaron? Aaron!
I'm here!
I panicked.
I saw Fluffy and freaked.
Are you trying to kill me?
I'm sorry.
Come, get me out.
Get me out of it.
I can't see anything
through this.
Wardrobe! Chloe!
Oh! Yep, I'm here.
I'm over here.
I'm here, I'm here!
My foot keeps on getting stuck
in this dumbass pouch
every time.
Okay, diva. Calm down.
Hey, I'm sorry, Hannah.
Oh, no, you're fine.
Trust me, I'm not a real diva.
Just playing the part of one.
But you don't know that.
You stay scared.
Scram!
Hannah. Hannah, darling.
You and Aaron need to practice.
Uh, Mr. Willis, I missed
my cue. It's my fault.
Tatum... a word.
We need to talk about
your Fluffy.
Yeah, I can't see
through Fluffy's eyes.
It's more than that.
You're very lackluster.
Fluffy needs energy.
Dogs are lively creatures.
You're too timid. Tatum,
where's your confidence?
You need to bring
more strength to this role.
I'll work on that.
You're Sidney Prescott's
daughter.
You need to channel
some of your mother's fire.
I'm surprised really.
I thought you had more grit.
Well, that was rude.
You're playing a dog.
Your only line is "Woof."
It's not that deep.
Hey, fuck him.
Yeah, fuck him.
Ah, don't let Willis get to you.
Your Fluffy's incredible.
Thanks, guys.
Um...
Okay, I'm...
I'm gonna go take this off.
I'll help you.
Uh, don't forget.
Party tonight.
My place.
All right.
Whoo!
Mmm!
Ugh.
Get me out of this thing.
I got it.
That's it.
Am I timid?
Oh, don't let that asshole
get to you.
Answer the question.
Be honest.
I wouldn't say timid, no, but
you have
this really cute shy quality.
"Shy" means "timid," FYI.
Do you think I lack confidence?
I can't win this.
I'm not playing.
Why do you like me?
That's a really long list.
Okay.
Well, be specific. One thing.
No.
It's... It's cheesy.
Say it anyway.
Okay.
I like how you look at me
in a certain way.
And it makes me smile.
Or you say something
that makes me laugh,
and I'll go home
and I'll think about it later
and I'll smile
and laugh all over again.
I really like that.
That wasn't cheesy.
That was a great answer.
- Hello.
- Hello, Sidney.
Guess who. Did you miss me?
I see you found
a new town to live in.
It reminds me a lot of
where we grew up.
Oh, do we know each other?
We sure do.
In fact, I was just
in Woodsboro last night.
Things got a little... heated.
But I'm here in Pine Grove now.
Yeah? What brings you here?
You, Sidney.
You were missed in New York.
It's not the same without you.
I guess you couldn't
be bothered now that you're
so busy with a husband
and family.
Well, you sure know
a lot about me
for another asshole
hiding behind
a fake number
and a voice changer.
Oh, I'm not hiding,
Sidney. Not this time.
Surprise, Sidney.
Do you need a minute? Oh!
Oh, my gosh.
It looks like you need
a minute. I'll wait.
Nice try. Stu Macher is dead.
Oh, gosh.
I'm gonna agree to
disagree with you there.
Oh, my God!
It is so good to see you.
I always had
a thing for you, Sid!
It's gonna be so much fun.
Just like the old days,
except now there's no Billy
or Randy or Tatum.
Speaking of whom, your daughter,
her name's Tatum.
That is so adorable.
I mean, It's a little weird or
whatever, but it's supercute.
And she is
so pretty.
Do not talk about my daughter.
Oh. Okay, yeah.
I should definitely
tell you, though,
I am currently outside of
her high school theater.
Don't you fucking dare!
It's showtime, bitch.
Hey, Chief.
You're gonna want to hear this.
I just got a call from
the police in Woodsboro.
Just a sec.
Hey, babe.
You need to go to the theater
right now.
What? What...
There's a killer, Mark.
He's going for Tatum.
I'm on it. All available units
to the high school theater now!
I'm on my way, babe.
Mark, hurry.
Start with liftoffs
and landings, okay?
Got it.
Ready?
Ready.
Okay, a little hard
on the landing there.
Sorry.
It's just too jerky.
Softer.
Got it.
Huh?
Try it again.
Okay, any day now!
Oh.
Hey, Aaron?
Hello?
This is my nice voice.
Aaron?
Shit.
Aaron? I want to get down now.
Hello!
No! No!
Put me down...
This isn't funny...
Aaron!
No!
Help!
Get me out!
This hurts!
Aaron!
Hello!
What the fuck?
No, wait!
Shit!
Oh, my God, please!
No, wait!
Hey, you stay away from me!
Get away!
No, please, wait!
Please! Please!
Please!
Stop, please! Please, please!
I don't want to die!
Tatum!
Motherfucker!
Cover the exits!
Oh, God. Okay.
Tatum!
Mom, what are you doing?
Oh, God!
Are you okay?
Oh, good... okay... okay.
I wasn't even here.
I had already left.
He was home with me.
Okay. Where were you?
I was downstairs
in the costume shop.
Not when I was there.
Wait, you were here?
No, he left and I was there.
But I didn't see you.
I was in the dressing rooms.
The whole time?
No. Not the whole time.
I went home,
had a light dinner,
Aperol Spritz.
My God, who would do
something like this?
We don't even
have an understudy.
Hey.
So, the killer fled.
Whoever did this
knew their way around here.
It was well-thought-out
and executed.
What about the kids?
Did you call your mom?
I called.
The entire Denver police force
is with them, they're safe.
Two teens are dead.
Mark, what the fuck?
You are not alone.
We got this.
If this is Stu...
It's not Stu.
It's not.
He is buried in Woodsboro.
Look, we are taking that
phone call that you recorded,
we're sending it
to the state police.
They have the resources
to determine who it is.
We are gonna get him.
Isn't Ben a computer junkie?
Aren't all kids?
He applied to Carnegie Mellon
to study computer science.
I hear you.
But anybody can do
deepfakes these days.
Why don't you get Tatum?
Just give me a minute and then
we'll get out of here.
Tatum, we're going.
Not you.
Mom.
Answer's no.
But, Mrs. Evans...
No.
It's okay.
You go with your family.
I'll call you.
Why do you treat him like that?
He's not a killer.
You don't know that.
Not everyone is Billy Loomis.
Just because you can't
trust people,
doesn't mean people can't
be trusted.
We're not doing this here.
They'll sweep the house.
Yeah. We'll be quick, Chief.
All clear.
We're gonna
secure the neighborhood.
Great.
We'll only be a few minutes.
Come on.
Thank you.
Grab your stuff.
You leave in five.
Wait. You're not
coming with us?
It's my job to catch
whoever's doing this.
Where's your go bag?
I unpacked it a long time ago.
Damn it, Tatum.
So, what? We just run?
Yes, we do.
I thought the great
Sidney Prescott never ran.
With you it's different.
They killed Hannah, Mom.
We can't just leave.
Listen, I know this story,
and if we stay,
more people will die.
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna
risk you getting hurt.
Why didn't you warn me?
About what?
All of this!
If-If I was ready,
maybe I could have saved her.
Maybe I could have
done something.
If you need anything else,
pack it.
Mom, why can't you just
trust me?
We need to go! Okay?
Here, take these.
Why did you turn the light out?
I thought you did.
Tatum.
Stay behind me.
Dad.
Please, leave her alone.
Mark, put the gun down.
Hon, it's gonna be okay.
Just look at me.
It's me that you want.
You just... you let her go.
Drop!
Mark!
Dad!
Run!
This way!
What-What are you doing?
Fuck off!
Where are we?
We're safe in here.
You sure he can't get inside?
Yeah.
What is that?
It's another way out.
I need to get your dad.
You stay here.
No, you can't leave me, Mom!
Let me go with you, please!
Okay, hurry.
Down to the end. Go.
Okay.
Shh.
Mom!
This way!
Go, go, go!
Okay.
Shh...
Go, go, go!
Mom!
Go!
Okay. This way.
Get the police! Go!
Mom!
Help! Somebody help us!
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
God, I love you.
I love you.
Did I get him?
You got him!
Chad, get the camera now.
Mindy, set up for a remote.
Ma'am, you need to stay
inside your vehicle.
You need to get out of my face.
Mom! Dad!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh, that was horrifying.
That was awesome.
Grab the camera.
We need B-roll of everything.
You have to be ready
at all times.
In my defense,
I wasn't exactly expecting
to be part
of vehicular manslaughter
the second we roll into town,
but next time...
next time I will be prepared.
Hey.
Chief, you gonna be okay?
Put pressure on it.
Just sit still for a minute.
You're bleeding.
Your point?
How's Mark?
It takes a lot
to bring him down.
Gale, he said he was Stu.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
Stu.
Stu Macher?
Dead Stu Macher?
Let's unmask this fucker.
Chief?
Do it.
Who is that?
I don't know, but I saw him
today in the coffee shop.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Nobody knows the guy?
Okay, that's weird.
That is weird. It's always
someone you know.
You want more B-roll?
We could make a whole movie.
I don't know what to say.
I meant to brake
and I hit the gas.
Karl Allen Gibbs.
He escaped from Fallbrook
Psychiatric Hospital
two weeks ago.
Triple murderer.
Any idea why he'd come after
you or your family?
No.
Thanks, Cooke.
Chief.
Well...
He's not gonna hurt anyone else.
No.
This was too easy.
There's always more than one.
Sidney,
Stu Macher is dead.
Watch Tatum for a minute.
Sidney. Sidney!
One question for you, Sidney!
Can we have a word?
Sidney! What's going on?
Over here!
Can you tell us anything?
What's happening, Sidney?
What's going on?
Sidney!
The network texted.
They want us to go live.
I'll go get Gale.
No! Don't.
No. No, I'm not doing this.
Yes.
They didn't specify
it had to be Gale.
You'll get us fired!
Do it! Come on!
Fine.
Three, two, one... Oh, boy.
You try that again, and I'll
rip both your throats out.
Got it?
Copy that.
We just learned
that Gale Weathers
from the now defunct talk show
Good Morning with
Gale Weathers is in town.
Excuse me, Miss Weathers.
Robbie Rivers, WFPO.
May I ask...
Fuck the fuck off.
Okay.
You two are a familiar sight.
What are you doing in town?
Just passing through.
With Gale Weathers?
And you just happened
to run over
an escaped mental patient
in front of Sidney Evans's home?
What's really going on here?
Why don't you
get your own story, Robbie.
Yeah, we're not here
to do it for you.
Come on, give a small-town
reporter his big break!
Hey, Sidney.
I'm so sorry this is happening
again, Mrs. Prescott.
Mrs. Evans, Lucas.
Right, yeah. Uh...
Sorry, that's what I meant.
Lucas, do you know
anything about A.I.?
A.I.? Uh, I refuse.
That is the death
of civilization.
Why are you asking that?
Just be careful, Jess.
Keep your doors locked.
Okay, come on, let's go.
Oh, you're Gale Weathers. Hey.
And who are you?
Uh...
I'm Lucas.
What are you doing here?
He's my son,
and we live next door.
We're friends
of the family.
Hmm.
Yeah.
You like horror movies, Lucas?
Yeah, I lo... I love them.
Especially the Stab movies?
Yeah,
I know them inside and out.
What are you doing?
Mom, it's Gale Weathers.
The Stab movies were based
on her true crime bestseller,
The Woodsboro Murders.
I know, but I don't like
the way she's looking at you.
Please leave my son out of
whatever it is you're doing.
Sorry, kid,
but you know how this works.
Yeah.
Everyone's a suspect.
Well, yeah, but you killed
the killer. He's dead.
Hmm.
How do you know
there's just one?
Excuse me.
Whoa.
Until this is over, I want you
to stay away from this house.
Come on, let's go.
How did you know to come?
When the news broke
about the two murders
at the Macher house,
a flock of reporters
raced to get there, but...
my Sidney-sense told me
that Woodsboro was played out.
Mark is having
the recorded calls analyzed
to confirm they're fake.
Is it possible they're real?
Could Stu be alive?
That would be
the better story,
but it's... too far-fetched.
Hmm.
What's going on?
Oh, I just have
some nerve damage from the...
from the attack in New York.
You're lucky you sat
that one out.
It-It was brutal.
Thank you.
It's nice to meet you, Tatum.
Mmm. Tatum?
Tatum as in...
That Tatum.
Yeah.
What do you two do for Gale?
We're her hot interns.
Ever since she got axed,
she's been trying to
go back to her roots.
So she's rebranding herself
as a crime reporter.
She's teaching us
all she knows about the biz.
Don't say "biz."
Yep.
It's more like we're showing
Gale the ropes
of making premium content.
Don't say "content."
It's going great.
Except Mindy keeps trying to
steal Gale's thunder.
I'm the face of the future.
Sure.
But in the meantime,
we're learning all about
fading careers
and failed comebacks.
Where are we gonna start?
S-Start what? I'm...
I'm not starting anything.
We have to find out
who's behind this.
That guy in the road,
Karl Gibbs,
is not some random killer.
It's always someone
connected to your past.
The police can handle it.
That would be your husband.
And we need to help him.
Don't you want to
know who's behind this?
Gale, I can't anymore.
I need to be with my family,
I need to know they're safe.
That's why you need to help me.
Whoever is targeting you
is not gonna stop...
you know that.
Oh, slap my face, if it
isn't the Gale Weathers!
Hi. Oh, my God,
I am so sorry
your show got canceled
and then you got fired.
I wasn't fired.
My contract wasn't renewed.
So don't care.
Not even a little.
Ugh. I'm so sorry for
running over your friend.
Can't do your own
dirty work, Stu?
Neither can you.
You brought in some old,
irrelevant hag for backup.
It's so sad.
And what happened to
the two of you?
You both had so much spunk.
You're gonna die,
you A.I. asshole.
We're going to see how fake I am
when I stab you
in the fucking throat!
Because I'm coming for you
and I'm gonna love
every second of it.
That was fucking weird.
Fallbrook Psychiatric Hospital.
It's a couple hours away.
We'll start there.
There she is.
I knew you were
in there somewhere.
You're right. This isn't
gonna stop unless I stop it.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Mom, I want to go with you.
No, sweetie, it's not safe.
So why are you going?
Because I know what I'm doing.
Mom, please.
You don't have
the skill set for this.
Well, then show me.
I don't want to end up like
the other Tatum.
What?
You named me after a girl who
got her head crushed
in a garage door.
She was my friend.
And she's dead!
She was a-a victim,
not a fighter.
I want to be a fighter.
Honey. Listen...
Nice to know what
you think of me.
She just lost a friend,
so... she's upset.
I want you to keep
her away from Ben.
He's not to come over here.
Someone was hiding
in the attic.
It could have been him.
We are running traces on
all her friends' cell numbers,
emails and IP's.
If Ben or any of her friends
are connected in any way
we're gonna find it.
She's right, you know.
Me protecting her from this,
I made her vulnerable to it.
Right.
Okay.
Okay, Terry. Thanks again.
Woodsboro coroner says
there's no intake form
on Stu Macher's body.
The woman who was coroner
in '96 died three years ago,
so there's no one to ask.
So it's a case
of lost paperwork?
Or stolen paperwork.
Someone who wants to
make it look like Stu's body
never made it to the morgue.
Or...
It's actually Stu.
Let's find out.
Yep.
Here's your pass.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
How can I help you?
Hi, I'm Gale Weathers.
I'm a reporter
for Channel 7 in New York.
Mm-hmm.
We're doing a story
on Karl Gibbs.
I figured.
The state police,
they were here all night
going through his stuff.
Can we see his room?
Well...
Yeah, I guess so. Come on,
it's right down this way.
So what can you
tell us about Karl?
He was a pretty violent guy.
Killed three women
about 20 years ago.
Can you think of any reason
that he would
go after Sidney Prescott
and her family?
No, not that I know of.
I'm glad you're okay, though.
Thanks.
Did you ever hear him talk
about the Ghostface killings?
Or the Stab movies,
or anything like that?
Not that I remember.
What about, um...
him?
Yeah, that's John.
John?
Yeah, as in John Doe.
He didn't know his real name.
He had amnesia from
the blow to the head
that gave him all those scars.
When did he arrive here?
Well, it was before my time.
I've been here 16 years.
So late '90s, maybe?
His room was right down there.
You want to see it?
Yes.
You know, h-he was a drifter.
Sleeping on the streets
of California or somewhere.
And then one day he snapped.
Attacked a high school girl.
He was declared incompetent to
stand trial and ended up here.
And where is he now?
He was released.
Two weeks ago.
Any idea where he went
after he was released?
No, I'm sorry.
But for that information
you're gonna need a court order.
And I assume that John Doe
and Karl Gibbs
spent a lot of time together?
Oh, yeah.
No, they were good friends.
Yeah.
Very close.
Hmm.
Neighbor boy's sus.
He's out there
staring at the house.
Not subtle at all.
I've gone back three days.
If the killer was hiding
in the attic,
he had to go into
the house at some point.
Could the footage be hacked?
Clearly the killer
is tech savvy.
I don't know.
Uh, did you two find the towels?
You got everything you need?
Yeah, the water pressure was...
top-notch, so, thank you.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
So, um...
Why are you here?
I'm sorry, I mean, um...
After everything
you've been through,
aren't you scared?
Scared. Necessity.
My career trajectory
is to succeed
and exceed Gale Weathers.
And as Woodsboro legacy,
it is our duty.
Our uncle Randy was really
good friends with your mom.
And I want to uncover
the killer this time.
She has been wrong a lot.
That is not supportive.
Un-Uncover a killer?
How do you uncover a killer?
Assemble the suspects
and then Agatha Christie them
until they break.
So... How do you
know who they are?
If history is any indication,
it's likely
one of your friends.
Probably your boyfriend.
Boyfriend's too obvious.
Unless it's by design.
It's not my boyfriend.
That's cute.
We need to gather all the
suspects together in one room.
Well, there's
a curfew at sundown.
The whole town's closing up.
Actually, there might be a way.
I just would have to figure
out how to get around my dad.
Is that possible?
He is the police chief.
But if we can find out
who's doing this,
then he can go get them.
If we can help, we should.
I'm sick of being useless.
That was Deputy Cooke.
They're set up to trace his
phone if he calls me again.
So we just have to
wait for him to call?
Oh, come on,
there's got to be some way to
bait him into calling you.
What if I gave you what you've
been asking me for since 1996?
An interview.
Get the fuck out of here.
Look, I just need an ETA
on that court order.
You got it, Chief.
I'll take care of it.
Good. Okay. Call me
the second Sid's phone rings.
Tatum!
Okay.
Get home safe. Bye, guys.
Hey.
Hey, Chlo.
Ben and Lucas are already here.
All right. Uh,
this is Chad and Mindy.
Hi. I'm Chloe. Come on in.
So your parents own this place.
Yes, but they
don't know we're here,
so we got to lay low.
How you doing?
What are we drinking, kids?
Here is...
the
pepperoni and mushroom pizza.
- Thanks, Chlo.
- Thank you.
So what is the deal
with you two?
Um, they want to help
us find out who's doing this.
What, they think it's one of us?
Yeah. But I don't.
So this dead dude from thirty
years ago, he is not so dead?
How could Stu Macher
really be alive?
Where's he been? Under a rock?
Nobody recognized him
for three decades?
That's a ridiculous retcon
for any franchise.
See, this time it is
all about nostalgia.
Hey, Min! We talked about
the rules thing,
we said we weren't gonna
do that anymore. We're better
than that. So just...
Okay. Whoever it is
wants to bring Sidney
out of retirement.
She's a scream queen.
Scream queens are not allowed
to have happy endings.
There's a reason they
keep putting Jamie Lee
in new Halloween movies.
We all want to read
Wuthering Heights
again for the first time.
But this is real life.
Yes, exactly.
This person isn't a fan of
Stab movies,
they're a fan of
Sidney Prescott.
Not the Sidney of today, though.
The Sidney of thirty years ago.
The Sidney that was killing
Ghostfaces, like, once a year.
And the reason they're using
Stu Macher to fuck with her
is because he was
there at the start.
The night Sidney the
Avenging Angel was born.
Or it really is Stu.
I mean, Billy Loomis
had a secret love child,
so who the fuck knows anymore?
Where'd you get these calls?
Uh...
My mom's cloud. Can you
tell if they're fake or not?
If it's a fake,
it's a good one.
Hmm.
The shadows are consistent.
The eyes, hands, they all have
zero artifacts or pixilation.
I mean...
These might have
been live calls.
All right, well,
if it is Stu Macher
then we know
he has an accomplice.
He can't be in two
places at once, so...
who is it?
Why would any of us want to
terrorize Tatum and her mom?
Why indeed. Let's talk motive.
Pardon. Thank you.
Okay, Ben.
Mmm.
Does Sidney truly approve
of you as Tatum's boyfriend?
Moms never like the boyfriend.
That's Mommy 101, there.
And you're an interesting
mix of brawn and brains.
Nah. I like to work out
my body and my mind, yeah.
See, that's incredibly
bizarre to say out loud.
Chloe.
- Hey.
- Fun-loving. Everyone likes.
Excellent hair.
Seemingly has no motive.
That's me.
- I'm not buying it.
- Good.
I don't like a girl
that everyone likes.
It's boring.
Oh. See? That's motive.
Right? Boredom? Now we're
in Stu Macher territory.
And you, weird boy.
Okay.
You've displayed
an unsettling obsession with
all things Sidney Prescott.
She's a pinnacle in
the true-crime lexicon.
I'm not obsessed.
I'm just...
I'm, uh, fascinated.
Splitting hairs, young man.
Okay, my money's on boyfriend.
Yeah, my bet's on creepy kid.
Okay, I'm pretty fucking sick of
all this "creepy" shit,
all right?
I'm not creepy.
Creepy is kind of hot.
Oh.
Hey.
Can I have another beer?
You can have whatever you want.
And per our discussion,
this is my exclusive.
- That was the deal.
- Yeah, yeah. Got it.
- Okay.
- There you go.
Oh, okay.
Oh. There.
All right,
I have three cameras on you.
We'll be operating from
the control room.
We need your phone,
so when he calls...
Thank you.
All right, ladies,
we'll be ready to break into
every affiliate in the state
on your go.
Jesus, this is fucking awesome!
Okay.
Let's just hope that
Stu is watching.
Ready?
You gonna play nice?
Of course not.
I've been waiting for this
interview for thirty years.
And three, two...
Hi, I'm Gale Weathers
here for an exclusive interview
with Sidney Prescott.
What the hell?
My mom's going live on TV.
Channel 7.
Oh.
Welcome, Sidney. Hi.
Hi, Gale.
So everyone knows you as
the survivor of
many brutal attacks.
And I understand that
you and your family
are once again a target.
Can you explain
what's happening?
My family and I
have been attacked twice now
by someone claiming to be
Stu Macher.
But Stu was killed in Woodsboro
the night that he
and Billy Loomis attacked you.
Yes, but now I'm not so sure.
Is that why you're doing
this interview?
I want to talk to him.
What would you
like to say?
I want to know what he wants.
Why he's doing this
after all of these years.
I want him to know that
this doesn't need to continue.
Zoom in.
Tighter, tighter.
Whatever you need, let's talk.
Hmm.
Maybe he's too much of
a little bitch.
He always was the sidekick,
never the lead.
Is that what it is?
You want to be the lead?
Well, here you go.
Call me. You have a platform.
Oh, shit.
Maybe he hasn't tuned in yet.
Let's keep talking.
You and I have known
each other a long time.
A very long time, yes.
How would you describe
our relationship?
Complicated but enduring.
You wrote a book,
Out of Darkness,
about healing your trauma.
And yet you have
completely disappeared
from the public eye
for years now. Why?
It just seemed
the more I talked about it,
the more darkness came.
Mmm.
You have three children.
Tatum being your oldest.
She's seventeen?
I'd rather not talk about
my children.
Tatum is the same age
that you were
when this whole thing started.
That must have
a huge significance for you.
Like I said, I don't want to
talk about my kids.
And you named your kid Tatum
after the young girl who was
brutally murdered
all those years ago.
I named her after a childhood
friend whom I loved dearly.
She was the last friend
I ever trusted.
Mmm.
Sidney, do you ever worry about
passing your trauma on
to your children?
Or, even worse yet,
that they would be
the target of future killings?
Oh, shit.
Sidney?
Okay, Gale, stop.
Where's she going?
Okay, we'll be right back.
Or maybe not. Cut.
All right.
Um... Go to the outro
and stand by.
Wh...
That was unfair.
And dangerous!
But you disappeared, Sid.
People want to know.
I want to know!
I'm sorry.
Are you?
What if I had asked you
about Dewey on live TV?
What would you say?
Well, I'd say I'm fine.
Because that's what I
tell myself 500 times a day
just to get through the day.
This has been a Robbie Rivers
exclusive with Gale Weathers
and Pine Grove's very
own Sidney Prescott Evans.
We will be monitoring...
That was intense.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry this is happening.
And this...
This was a dumb idea.
How far is the TV station?
I just really want to be with
my mom right now.
We're super close.
I mean, I'll take you.
Okay.
We're not on air.
And this needs to be
on air.
Hello?
Aw, Sid, do you need a hug?
We've been waiting for you.
Why? So I can
stay on the phone
long enough for you to
trace the call?
Yes, dumbass! Or you could
just tell us where you are.
Great. I am at Parker's Tavern
with your daughter.
My daughter's not at Parker's.
Well, she's definitely not
at home.
She broke curfew.
She's a bad bitch.
I'm gonna punish her.
Fuck.
Is that it?
Is he gonna call back?
Because you said
this was my story.
Where's the story, Gale?
Stop!
You need to
call the police right now,
tell them to go to
Parker's Tavern.
Sidney!
Oh, fuck.
Mark, Tatum went
to Chloe's restaurant.
She's in trouble.
Where are you?
Damn it!
Oh, fuck.
Thanks.
What is this?
Hmm?
Oh, uh...
- Did you create this?
- What? No.
I created that one just
to see if it was possible.
I can't wait to fucking
kill you, Sidney Prescott,
and your daughter.
And I'm gonna love
every second of it, you bitch!
Tate.
It was you.
No, it wasn't.
Tate.
You know, not exactly
a roaring success, Min.
We still have no idea
who the killer is.
Creepy kid still has my vote.
I'm way too obvious.
So obvious it's not obvious.
What is that smell?
Oh, shit! Pizza's in the oven.
Bathroom break.
We should not have left Tatum
alone with Gen-Z Billy Loomis.
Okay? I'm not feeling good
about that.
Do you find it weird
that two very real suspects
just conveniently disappeared?
I really don't want
to get stabbed tonight.
Let's go find Tatum.
Okay.
It's locked.
We are locked in.
There must be
another way out of here.
Let's try the dining room.
Oven's a piece of shit.
Fuck.
Where's the fucking door?
Hey. The kitchen.
There has to be a back door.
That's not good.
Aw, shit.
Hey, cupcake!
Hey, hey, hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
The killer is in there.
Hey, hey. I got this.
Don't go in there.
It's okay, I got this.
I got this, I got this!
Lucas!
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Fuck.
Lucas.
No.
No. Help. No.
No, no, no. No!
No!
Open up, please! Please!
Come on!
Help! Please,
somebody help me!
He's trying to kill me!
Please!
Someone help me!
I found you.
Did you see him? The killer?
No, I didn't see anyone.
You hit me.
Got me real good, too.
We have to get out of here.
Tate, listen.
It's not me, Tate.
I know. I know, I'm sorry.
I would never hurt you, okay?
No!
Help!
Oh, God.
Tatum.
Mom!
I'm coming, okay?
He's at the door!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck you, phone.
I can't hear you!
Okay. Okay.
Tatum, listen to me.
I'm not gonna make it in time.
But I'm gonna stay with you.
You need to get the gun.
It's in the safe.
Okay.
The code is your birthday.
I don't know how to use this.
I'm gonna talk you through it.
You have your earbuds?
Well, put them in, okay?
You're gonna need both hands.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Wait.
I don't hear him.
I think he left.
No, he's trying to find
another way in.
Oh, Mom, hurry!
Okay, baby, listen to me.
The gun is...
It's loaded,
so you have to turn
the safety off, all right?
You see that little switch?
Flip it up. There's a red dot.
I see it.
Okay. So all you have to
do now is you point
and you pull the trigger.
You aim for center mass, okay?
And when he goes down,
you shoot him in the head.
I can't.
I'm not like you. I can't.
Tatum, you are.
You are like me.
I saw your interview.
Baby, focus.
We're gonna do this together.
He killed Ben.
He killed him.
Right now
you need to survive. Okay?
That is what's important
right now.
Okay.
You're gonna have to shoot him
through the wall.
Where?
Okay, you're gonna
shoot the calendar.
Fire through the calendar.
No, wait.
Wait. He's moving.
Mom?
To the right of the door.
Shoot him now! Do it now!
Oh, you got him.
You got him.
Okay.
Okay, listen, you're gonna
have to walk around him.
But before you do that,
you shoot him in the head.
But he's dead, I got him.
I know, baby.
You need to make sure.
You shoot him. You shoot him
in the head right now.
Tatum... Tatum!
Tatum!
Mom! Mom!
Hello, Sidney.
Are we having fun yet?
If you hurt her...
Relax.
I'm not going to hurt her
until you're here to see it.
Where are you?
Where the heart is...
until I stab a knife through it.
Come alone.
Welcome home, Sidney.
We've been waiting for you.
Waiting for you.
Thanks for coming alone.
It makes it so much easier
that you followed the rules.
Stop this shit.
If you're Stu, show yourself!
Where am I?
Can you find me?
It's not really me.
You want to know
who I really am?
Remember me?
I'll never forgive you for
what you did to my son.
And you know what?
I would do it again and again.
Your mother destroyed my life.
But let's face it.
She destroyed you, too.
In the same way that you've
destroyed your own daughter.
Fuck whoever you are!
Over here!
It's me, sis.
Do you want to make a movie?
Oh. How about a scary one?
I've been working on
this great script.
Come on, Sid.
We're family.
It really comes down to
family, doesn't it, Sid?
I mean, we both know how far
we'd go for our own family.
And friends, of course.
But all your friends die for
just being near you.
I died for you, Sidney.
Doesn't that
mean anything to you?
Where is my daughter?
I thought I'd go back to
where it all started.
A phone call, a girl,
and someone she cares about
tied to a chair
outside of her house.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Tatum, baby, I'm sorry.
Just...
What do you want from me?
Please tell me.
You.
Yeah. Me.
Well, me and Karl.
Karl is dead.
Mm-hmm.
And I would be, too,
but your daughter
missed my head.
You've always got to
shoot them in the head.
Okay, okay.
Isn't that right,
Stu?
Okay, okay.
I'll be right back.
Mark.
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Okay.
Look at that!
He's still alive.
That is a tough motherfucker.
Fuck you!
Jessica. What?
Hi, neighbor.
How you holding up?
You didn't really think
it was Stu?
Because that'd be dumb.
Stu's dead.
You know,
alive in spirit, but...
dead.
See,
I have a background in A.I.
I was a Google security
specialist once upon a time.
Before Fallbrook.
Bringing Stu back was my idea.
No, no, no, no, it was my idea.
No, I just let you think
it was your idea.
Jessica, please,
what are you doing?
"Oh, Jessica." "Oh, please."
"Oh, what are you doing?"
God, I don't recognize you.
I mean, what happened to you?
You know, you've really
let me down, Sid.
Listen to me. This isn't you.
Whatever this is,
there's another way.
Oh, I know.
There's always another way.
Excuse me.
You taught me that.
It's in your book.
You saved my life, Sidney.
Before you ruined it.
You know about
my abusive marriage, right?
I was really trapped,
and I couldn't see a way out.
But then I read
Out of Darkness
by Sidney Prescott.
Oh, it's such a great book!
And then I realized that
your life, it comes down to
one simple truth.
Sidney Prescott kills
the bad guy.
That's your purpose.
You are a real-life
scream queen.
The final girl.
God, you inspire me!
So I started planning
and doing Pilates,
and then I pulled a Sidney
and I killed my husband!
I got away with it, too.
And I had you to thank for it.
But then you went away, Sid!
And you didn't go to New York.
A Ghostface attack
doesn't count
if you're not there.
You disappeared.
Why, Sidney?
I wanted people to see
there was life after trauma.
But there isn't for you!
Trauma is your life.
When you disappeared,
do you know how much
that hurt me?
I mean,
I couldn't fucking handle it!
I checked myself
into a facility.
Fallbrook.
That's where we met.
Okay, I'm talking,
so don't interrupt me, okay?
Great. Fuck.
Where the fuck was I?
Shit. Fuck!
New York. Pilates.
You disappeared.
Fallbrook.
Fallbrook. Fallbrook, yes!
It was the closest psychiatric
center that I could find
because I had to be near you.
And that finally brings us
to tonight.
Okay, Jessica, you're right,
I've been selfish.
I can do better.
We can start over.
I am starting over.
By killing you.
No more baggage.
I am releasing it all.
What about Lucas?
You have a son.
Oh, no, no. He's gone, Sid.
I mean, he was too much
like his father.
And now
I can have a new beginning.
Do you think that you've been
a good mother to Tatum?
I mean, you really haven't
taught her anything useful,
am I right?
You've kept the survivor
all to yourself.
But that's okay.
Because I'm gonna teach her!
She's gonna watch
her mother die.
Just like you did.
The cycle continues.
No.
You see,
it finally dawned on me.
I don't need you.
I mean, none of us do.
Let's face it,
you're kind of past your prime
for a final girl.
I'm creating Sidney 2.0.
Watch closely, Tatum.
Okay.
Okay, honey,
you're gonna need
to call an ambulance. Okay?
What?
Mom! No, wait!
Where are you going?
Stay with your dad.
No, no, no, no, Mom! God, no!
Sidney.
Sidney...
Please.
Is that all you've got?
Fuck!
Are you okay?
You got to shoot her
in the head.
What?
Shoot her in the...
Shit!
Damn it. Okay.
Come on.
You okay?
I'm Sidney
fucking Prescott's daughter.
Past my prime.
Fuck you.
This is Robbie Rivers
with an exclusive
on the scene, live report,
at the home of
police chief Mark Evans,
where a bloody nightmare
has come to an end.
Network wants a live remote.
No way. Too much blood loss.
I can't hold a camera.
I was hoping you'd do it.
I do feel better.
We're gonna need to frame out
the blood, though.
I'll get the tripod.
Thanks for ditching me.
Seriously, what was that about?
You have always
had my back, Gale.
I should have gone to New York.
I should have
been there for you.
No, Sid.
And I was wrong about something.
I do trust...
I trust you.
You want me to
drive you to the hospital?
I'd love that.
Okay.
Just give me a minute.
This is exactly what
I didn't want for you.
I don't think it was up to you.
Tatum was my best friend.
She was funny,
and outspoken.
Said whatever was on her mind.
No edit whatsoever.
And she was strong.
And fierce.
She wasn't afraid of anything.
So that's why I named you Tatum.
Because that was my wish
for you.
To be strong...
and unafraid.
What else can I tell you?
That's enough for now.
Okay.
You know I love you.
I love you more.
Let's go
see your dad.
Yeah.
Three, two...
It all began
last Thursday night
in Woodsboro, California,
at a house made infamous
for the stashing.
Cut. I got caught between
"stabbing" and "slashing".
Hey, you suck at this.
Shut up. Go again.
Copy that. Three, two...
Hi. I'm Mindy Meeks-Mar...
I don't know.
You messed up
your own name, dude?
Stop laughing!
Okay. Three, two...
Hi. I'm Mindy Meeks-Martin,
three-time Ghostface survivor
and new reporter
for CBS 7, New York.
Oh, my God, I wasn't recording any of that.
One second.
I hate you.